<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GhumKe</string>
    <string name="lucknow">Lucknow, the capital of Uttar Pradesh was historically known as the Awadh region.
    Today, it is the administrative headquarters of Lucknow District and Lucknow Division.
    Fondly known as the ‘City of Nawabs’ or the ‘City of Tehzeeb’, it has always been a city filled with varied cultures.
        Its beautiful sprawling gardens, polite mannerisms, fine-cuisine, music, and poetry (Shayari), had found a patronage in the Shia Nawabs of the city who loved Persian.
The city has been given various other names too, such as The Constantinople of India, Shiraz-i-Hind and the Golden City of the East.
Today, it is known as one of the most important cities of the country which is now emerging in various sectors like retailing, manufacturing and commercial.
Lucknow city has to offer a unique feature to its travelers, which is a perfect combination of its rich traditions and the modern growth of new-mannerisms. The same is its USP. After Kanpur, it is the second largest city of Uttar Pradesh.
    </string>


    <string name="rumi">The Rumi Darwaza, in Lucknow,
        Uttar Pradesh, India, is an imposing gateway 
        which was built under the patronage of Nawab Asaf-Ud-dowlah in 1784.
        It is an example of Awadhi architecture.</string>
    <string name="chowk">It is an ancient market in the heart of Uttar Pradesh\'s capital Lucknow
        It is famous for its chikan work, which is a cloth embroidered with hands.Chowk in lucknow is the
        world wide expoter of this unique handicraft.
    </string>
    <string name="clock">Husainabad Clock Tower is a clock tower located in the Lucknow city of India.
        It was constructed in 1881 by Nawab Nasir-ud-din Haider to mark the arrival of Sir George Couper,
        1st Lieutenant Governor of United Province of Avadh. It was built at a cost of Rs. 1.75 lakhs</string>
    <string name="imambara">Bara Imambara (बड़ा इमामबाड़ा) is an imambara complex in Lucknow, India,
        built by Asaf-ud-Daula, Nawab of Awadh, in 1784. It is also called the Asafi Imambara.
Bara means big, and an imambara is a shrine built by Shia Muslims for the purpose of Azadari.
        The Bara Imambara is among the grandest buildings of Lucknow.</string>


    <string name="ahe">Ahmedabad also known as Amdavad is the largest city and former capital of Gujarat,
        which is a state in India. It is the administrative headquarters of the Ahmedabad district and the
        seat of the Gujarat High Court. With a population of more than 6.3 million and an extended population of 7.8 million,
        it is the sixth largest city and seventh largest metropolitan area of India. Ahmedabad is located on the banks of the
        Sabarmati River, 30 km (19 mi) from the state capital Gandhinagar, which is its twin city.
        Ahmedabad has emerged as an important economic and industrial hub in India. It is the second largest producer of cotton
        in India, and its stock exchange is the country\'s second oldest. Cricket is a popular sport in Ahmedabad, which houses the
        54,000-seat Sardar Patel Stadium. The effects of liberalisation of the Indian economy have energised the city\'s economy
        towards tertiary sector activities such as commerce, communication and construction.Ahmedabad\'s increasing population has
        resulted in an increase in the construction and housing industries resulting in recent development of skyscrapers.</string>

    <string name="a2">Sabarmati Ashram (also known as Gandhi Ashram, Harijan Ashram, or Satyagraha Ashram) is located in the Sabarmati suburb
        of Ahmedabad, Gujarat, adjoining the Ashram Road, on the banks of the River Sabarmati, four miles from the town hall.
        This was one of the residences of Mohandas Karamchand Gandhi.</string>

    <string name="a3">Kankaria Lake, formerly known as Hauz e Qutub, is the second largest lake in Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India.
        It is located in the south-eastern part of the city, in the Maninagar area.</string>

    <string name="a4">A holy and a spiritual place for sikhs. This is the biggest and famous Gurudwara in city. When there are
        occasions they set up amazing lights and when it comes to langar they have very decent food but they will serve with
        feelings and you will be amazed to see them. </string>

    <string name="a5">The Sidi Saiyyed Mosque more popularly known as "Sidi Saiyyid ki Jaali" (Sidi Saiyyed Ni Jaali), built in
        1573, is one of the most famous mosques of Ahmedabad. As attested by the marble tablet fixed on the wall of the mosque,
        it was built by Sidi Saeed or Sidi Saiyyed, an Abyssinian in the retinue of Bilal Jhajar Khan, general in the army of the
        last Sultan Shams-ud-Din Muzaffar Shah III of the Gujarat Sultanate.</string>


    <string name="ban">Bangalore , officially known as Bengaluru, is the capital of the Indian state of Karnataka.
        It has a population of about 8.42 million and a metropolitan population of about 8.52 million, making it the third
        most populous city and fifth most populous urban agglomeration in India.It is located in southern India on the
        Deccan Plateau. Its elevation is over 900 m (3,000 ft) above sea level, the highest of India\'s major cities.
         Bangalore is sometimes referred to as the "Silicon Valley of India" (or "IT capital of India") because of its
        role as the nation\'s leading information technology (IT) exporterIndian technological organisations ISRO, Infosys,
        Wipro and HAL are headquartered in the city. A demographically diverse city, Bangalore is the second fastest-growing
        major metropolis in India.</string>

    <string name="b2">Dodda Basavana Gudi is situated in Bull Temple Road, Basavanagudi, area of South Bangalore, part of
            the largest city of the Indian state of Karnataka. The Hindu temple is inside a park called Bugle Rock</string>

    <string name="b3">Wonderla Holidays Limited is a leading amusement park designing and operating company in India
            headquartered near Bidadi, 28 kilometres (17 mi) from Bangalore. It is promoted by Kochouseph Chittilappilly and
            his son Arun Chittilappilly. </string>

    <string name="b4">Bannerghatta National Park, near Bangalore, Karnataka, was founded in 1970 and declared as a national park
            in 1974. In 2002 a portion of the park, became a biological reserve, the Bannerghatta Biological Park.</string>

    <string name="b5">Venkatappa Art Gallery is situated Bangalore, India, in the vicinity of Cubbon Park and next to the
            Bangalore Museum as well as the Visvesvaraya Industrial and Technological Museum. It attracts artists and art lovers
            from all over Karnataka.</string>


    <string name="che">Chennai formerly known as Madras is the capital of the Indian state of Tamil Nadu. Located on the
        Coromandel Coast off the Bay of Bengal, it is one of the biggest cultural, economic and educational centres in South India.
        According to the 2011 Indian census, it is the sixth-largest city and fourth-most populous urban agglomeration in India.
        The city together with the adjoining regions constitute the Chennai Metropolitan Area, which is the 36th-largest urban area
        by population in the world.Chennai is among the most visited Indian cities by foreign tourists. It was ranked 43rd most
        visited city in the world for year 2015.The Quality of Living Survey rated Chennai as the safest city in India.Chennai
        attracts 45 percent of health tourists visiting India, and 30 to 40 percent of domestic health tourists.The Chennai Metropolitan
        Area is one of the largest city economies of India. Chennai is nicknamed "The Detroit of India", with more than one-third of
        India\'s automobile industry being based in the city. </string>

    <string name="c2">The Kālikāmbal Temple is a Hindu temple dedicated to Shri Kāligāmbāl and Lord Kamadeswarar,
        located in Parry\'s corner locality of the city of Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India.</string>

    <string name="c3">Guindy National Park is a 2.70 km2 (1.04 sq mi) Protected area of Tamil Nadu, located in Chennai, South India,
        is the 8th smallest National Park of India and one of the very few national parks situated inside a city. The park is an
        extension of the grounds surrounding Raj Bhavan, formerly known as the \'Guindy Lodge\', the official residence of the
        Governor of Tamil Nadu, India. It extends deep inside the governor\'s estate, enclosing beautiful forests, scrub lands,
        lakes and streams.</string>

    <string name="c4">The Tirupati Tirumala Devasthanam Temple is dedicated to Sri Vishnu as Srinivasa Perumal and Divine Mother
        Shakti as Padmavathi Thayar.</string>

    <string name="c5">San Thome Basilica is a Roman Catholic minor basilica in Santhome, in the city of Chennai, India. It was built in
        the 16th century by Portuguese explorers, over the tomb of Saint Thomas, one of the twelve apostles of Jesus</string>


    <string name="del">Delhi, officially the National Capital Territory of Delhi or NCT, is a city and a union territory of India.
        It is bordered by Haryana on three sides and by Uttar Pradesh to the east. The NCT covers an area of 1,484 square
        kilometres (573 sq mi). According to 2011 census, Delhi\'s city population was about 11 million,the second highest in India
        after Mumbai, while the whole NCT population was about 16.8 million.Delhi\'s urban area is now considered to extend beyond
        the NCT boundary to include an estimated population of over 26 million people making it the world\'s second largest urban
        area.As of 2016 recent estimates of the metro economy of its urban area have ranked Delhi either the top or second most
        productive metro area of India.Delhi is the second wealthiest city after Mumbai in India, with a total wealth of $450
        billion and home to 18 billionaires and 23,000 millionaires. Delhi has been continuously inhabited since the 6th century
        BC.Through most of its history, Delhi has served as a capital of various kingdoms and empires. It has been captured,
        ransacked and rebuilt several times, particularly during the medieval period, and modern Delhi is a cluster of a number
        of cities spread across the metropolitan region. A union territory, the political administration of the NCT of Delhi today
        more closely resembles that of a state of India, with its own legislature, high court and an executive council of ministers
        headed by a Chief Minister. New Delhi is jointly administered by the federal government of India and the local government
        of Delhi, and is the capital of the NCT of Delhi. Delhi hosted the first and ninth Asian Games in 1951 and 1982
        respectively, 1983 NAM Summit, 2010 Men\'s Hockey World Cup, 2010 Commonwealth Games, 2012 BRICS Summit and was one of
        the major host cities of the 2011 Cricket World Cup.</string>

    <string name="d2">Qutub Minar is a minaret that forms part of the Qutb complex, a UNESCO World Heritage Site in the
            Mehrauli area of Delhi, India. Its design is thought to have been based on the Minaret of Jam, in western Afghanistan.
        </string>
    <string name="d3">The Lotus Temple, located in Delhi, India, is a Bahá\'í House of Worship completed in 1986. Notable
            for its flowerlike shape, it serves as the Mother Temple of the Indian subcontinent and has become a prominent
            attraction in the city.</string>
    <string name="d4">kshardham or Swaminarayan Akshardham complex is a Hindu mandir, and a spiritual-cultural campus in
            New Delhi, India.</string>
    <string name="d5">Gurudwara Bangla Sahib; (Punjabi: ਗੁਰਦੁਆਰਾ ਬੰਗਲਾ ਸਾਹਿਬ) is one of the most prominent Sikh gurdwara,
            or Sikh house of worship, in Delhi, India and known for its association with the eighth Sikh Guru, Guru Har Krishan,
            as well as the pool inside its complex, known as the Sarovar</string>


    <string name="hyd">Hyderabad is the capital of the southern Indian state of Telangana and de jure capital of Andhra Pradesh.
        Occupying 650 square kilometres (250 sq mi) along the banks of the Musi River, it has a population of about 6.7 million
        and a metropolitan population of about 7.75 million, making it the fourth most populous city and sixth most populous urban
        agglomeration in India. At an average altitude of 542 metres (1,778 ft), much of Hyderabad is situated on hilly terrain
        around artificial lakes, including Hussain Sagar—predating the city\'s founding—north of the city centre.
        Hyderabad was historically known as a pearl and diamond trading centre, and it continues to be known as the City of
        Pearls. Many of the city\'s traditional bazaars remain open, including Laad Bazaar, Begum Bazaar and Sultan Bazaar.
        Industrialisation throughout the 20th century attracted major Indian manufacturing, research and financial institutions,
        including Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited, the National Geophysical Research Institute and the Centre for Cellular and
        Molecular Biology. Special economic zones dedicated to information technology have encouraged companies from India and
        around the world to set up operations in Hyderabad. The emergence of pharmaceutical and biotechnology industries in the
        1990s led to the area\'s naming as India\'s "Genome Valley". With an output of US$74 billion, Hyderabad is the fifth-largest
        contributor to India\'s overall gross domestic product.</string>

    <string name="h2">Golkonda, also known as Golconda, Gol konda, or Golla konda, is a citadel and fort in Southern India and
            was the capital of the medieval sultanate of the Qutb Shahi dynasty, is situated 11 kilometres west of Hyderabad.</string>
    <string name="h3">The Charminar, constructed in 1591, is a monument and mosque located in Hyderabad, Telangana, India. The landmark
            has become a global icon of Hyderabad, listed among the most recognized structures of India.</string>
    <string name="h4">Hussain Sagar is a heart shaped lake in Hyderabad built by Ibrahim Quli Qutub Shah in 1563, during the rule of
            Ibrahim Quli Qutub Shah. It is spread across an area of 5.7 square kilometers and is fed by River Musi.</string>
    <string name="h5">The Ramoji Film City in India is located in Hyderabad. At 1633 acres, it is the largest integrated film city in the world.</string>


    <string name="kol">Kolkata, also known as Calcutta ,is the capital of the Indian state of West Bengal. Located on the east
        bank of the Hooghly River, it is the principal commercial, cultural, and educational centre of East India, while the Port
        of Kolkata is India\'s oldest operating port and its sole major riverine port. In 2011, the city had a population of
        4.5 million, while the population of the city and its suburbs was 14.1 million, making it the third-most populous
        metropolitan area in India. Recent estimates of Kolkata Metropolitan Area\'s economy have ranged from $60 to
        $150 billion (GDP adjusted for purchasing power parity) making it third most-productive metropolitan area in India,
        after Mumbai and Delhi.In the late 17th century, the three villages that predated Calcutta were ruled by the Nawab of
        Bengal under Mughal suzerainty. After the Nawab granted the East India Company a trading licence in 1690,the area was
        developed by the Company into an increasingly fortified trading post. Nawab Siraj ud-Daulah occupied Calcutta in 1756,
        and the East India Company retook it the following year. In 1793 the East India company was strong enough to abolish
        Nizamat (local rule), and assumed full sovereignty of the region. </string>

    <string name="k2">The Victoria Memorial is a large marble building in Kolkata, West Bengal, India, which was built between
        1906 and 1921.</string>
    <string name="k3">The Indian Museum is the largest and oldest museum in India and has rare collections of antiques, armour
        and ornaments, fossils, skeletons, mummies, and Mughal paintings. It was founded by the Asiatic Society of Bengal in
        Kolkata, India, in 1814.</string>
    <string name="k4">Kalighat Kali Temple is a Hindu temple in West Bengal, India dedicated to the Hindu goddess Kali. It is one
        of the 51 Shakti Peethas. Kalighat was a Ghat sacred to Kali on the old course of the Hooghly river in the
        city of Calcutta.</string>
    <string name="k5">Eden Gardens is a cricket ground in Kolkata, India. It has also been used for Association football matches. It was established in 1864.</string>


    <string name="mum" formatted="false">Mumbai also known as Bombay is the capital city of the Indian state of Maharashtra. It is the most
        populous city in India and the ninth most populous agglomeration in the world, with an estimated city population of
        18.4 million. Along with the neighbouring regions of the Mumbai Metropolitan Region, it is one of the most populous
        urban regions in the world and the second most populous metropolitan area in India, with a population of 20.7 million
        as of 2011.Mumbai lies on the west coast of India and has a deep natural harbour. In 2008, Mumbai was named an alpha
        world city.It is also the wealthiest city in India,and has the highest GDP of any city in South, West, or Central Asia.
        Mumbai has the highest number of billionaires and millionaires among all cities in India. Mumbai is the financial,
        commercial and entertainment capital of India. It is also one of the world\'s top ten centres of commerce in terms of
        global financial flow,generating 6.16% of India\'s GDP and accounting for 25% of industrial output, 70% of maritime
        trade in India (Mumbai Port Trust and JNPT)and 70% of capital transactions to India\'s economy.The city houses important
        financial institutions such as the Reserve Bank of India, the Bombay Stock Exchange, the National Stock Exchange of India,
        the SEBI and the corporate headquarters of numerous Indian companies and multinational corporations.
    </string>

    <string name="m2">The Gateway of India is a monument built during the 20th century in Mumbai City of Maharashtra state in
        Western India. It is located on the waterfront in the Apollo Bunder area in South Mumbai and overlooks the Arabian Sea.
    </string>
    <string name="m3">The Haji Ali Dargah is a mosque and dargah located on an islet off the coast of Worli in the southern part
        of Mumbai. Near the heart of the city proper, the dargah is one of the most recognisable landmarks of Mumbai.
    </string>
    <string name="m4">The Shree Siddhivinayak Ganapati Mandir is a Hindu temple dedicated to Lord Shri Ganesh. It is located in
        Prabhadevi, Mumbai, Maharashtra.</string>
    <string name="m5">EsselWorld is an amusement park located in Gorai, Mumbai and established in 1989. The park is owned by Pan India
        Paryatan Pvt. Ltd. EsselWorld along with its counterparts, Water Kingdom are stretched over 64 acres of land.</string>


</resources>
